Preliminary Inventory of the Ohio State University, Internal Audit Records, 1897-2000 RG.6.B.2
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
Ohio State University, Internal Audit Records
1897-2000
RG.6.B.2
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
20.4 Cubic feet
Ohio State University. Department of Internat Auditing.
Ohio State University. Internal Audit.
Arrangement of Materials
Materials are arranged in the order received.
Acquisitions Information
Accession Number UA.1972.0041: Auditor's Office, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1981.0036: Internatl Auditing, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1982.0001: Internal Auditing, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1982.0076: Internal Affairs, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1984.0095: Source unknown, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1985.0187: Internal Auditing, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1986.0140: Vice President Jackson, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1988.0081: Source unknown, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1988.0083: Source unknown, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1988.0091: Source unknown, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1989.0121: Source unknown, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1993.0070: Source unknown, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1995.0077: Source unknown, date unknown; Accession Number UA.1997.0001: Kevin Patton, date unknown; Accession Number UA.2000.0065: Debi LePera, date unknown; Accession Number UA.2000.0077: Debi LePera, date unknown
Access to Materials
Materials in this collection are available for patron research, but may be used only in the University Archives Reading Room. Audiovisual materials may need a use copy produced before access is allowed. Some materials in this collection may be stored off-site, and are only available if requested 72 hours in advance of your visit. Contact the University Archives for more information..
Scope and Contents
This collection contains ledger books, reports, correspondence, and other administrative and financial records.
Ohio State University--History.; Ohio State University. Department of Internat Auditing.; Ohio State University. Internal Audit.
- Processed, 1962-1999; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  - Ledger Books and Sheets, undated (Box UA.RG.6.B.2.0001)
  - Ledger Books and Sheets: Conference Accounts (4 folders), 1953-1963 (Box UA.RG.6.B.2.0001)
  - Ledger Books and Sheets: Navy Accounts, 1942-1943 (Box UA.RG.6.B.2.0001)
  - Ledger Books and Sheets: Ohio Union (3 folders), 1920-1939 (Box UA.RG.6.B.2.0001)
  - Ledger Books and Sheets: Pomerene Board of Control (2 folders), 1922-1942 (Box UA.RG.6.B.2.0001)
  - Ledger Books and Sheets: Research Foundation (4 folders), 1937-1947 (Box UA.RG.6.B.2.0001)
  - Ledger Books and Sheets: Special Conference Funds (2 folders), 1960-1964 (Box UA.RG.6.B.2.0001)
- Accession Number UA.1981.0036, 1962-1980; 1.6 Cubic feet; (1) carton, (1) 5" letter document box
  Scope and Contents
  Audit reports for the hospital, Ohio Union, airport and other OSU offices. Includes Ernst and Ernst review of the Athletic Department.
  - Hospital Audit Report, 1970-1971 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 1)
  - Ohio Unions, 1975 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 2)
  - Ohio Airport, 1975 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 3)
  - Football Tickets, 1976 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 4)
  - Bookstores, 1976 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 5)
  - Physical Facilities, 1976 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 6)
  - Traffic and Parking, 1976 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 7)
  - Food Facilities, 1976 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 8)
  - Ernst and Ernst: Review of Athletic Department, 1970 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 9)
  - Humanities, 1976 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 10)
  - Audit Reports, 1962-1976,1977-1980 (Box UA.1981.0036.0001, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box UA.1981.0036.0002, Folder 1)
  - Lead File, 1979-1980 (Box UA.1981.0036.0002, Folder 2)
- Accession Number UA.1982.0001, 1980-1981; 0.5 Cubic feet; (1) 5" legal document box
  - Audit reports, 1980-1981 (Box UA.1982.0001.0001)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box UA.1982.0001.0001)
- Accession Number UA.1982.0076, 1981-1982; 0.4 Cubic feet; (1) 5" letter document box
  - Audit Reports, 1981-1982 (Box UA.1982.0076.0001)
  - Lead Files: correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box UA.1982.0076.0001)
- Accession Number UA.1984.0095, 1981-1982; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  - Audit Reports, 1981-1982 (Box UA.1984.0095.0001)
  - General Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box UA.1984.0095.0001)
- Accession Number UA.1985.0187, 1978-1983; 6.4 Cubic feet; (5) cartons; (1) 5" letter document box
  - Internal Audit Reports, undated (Box UA.1985.0187.0001)
  - General Correspondence, FY 1982-1983 (Box UA.1985.0187.0001)
  - Internal Audit Reports, UVC Admin, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Arts Admin, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, School of Music, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, University Theater, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Mershon, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Biochemistry, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Entomology, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Microbiology, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Zoology, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Humanities, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Black Studies, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Classics, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, German, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Romance Languages, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Math, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Astronomy, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Geology, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Lantern, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Psychology, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Mansfield, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Marion, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Youth Science Review, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Agriculture, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Natural Resources, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Home Economics, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Education, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Instructional Materials Lab, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Vocational Technical Education, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Distributive Education, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Engineering, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Landscape Architecture, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Computer and Information Sciences, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Engineering Experiment Station, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Metallurgical Engineering, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Photography, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Pharmacy, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Law Administration, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Veterinary Medicine, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Veterinary Clinic, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0002)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Student Financial Aid (work study), 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0004)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Child Care (petty cash), 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0004)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Contracts Administration (MacDonald's Sales), 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0004)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Contracts Administration (Pizza Hut), 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0004)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Business MGMT (Bookstores & Print Facility), 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0004)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Health Professions Loans, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Physical Facilities, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, University Police, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Traffic & Parking, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Food Facility, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Stores, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Laundry, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Office Equipment Repair, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Print Facility, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Transportation, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Administrative and Analysis, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Residence and Dining Halls, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Dorm Accounting, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Warner-Qube, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Gladieux Sales, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Athletics, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Golf Course Restaurant, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - OSU Bookstores, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0005)
  - Internal Audit Reports, OSU Bookstores, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Fawcett Center, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Ohio Union, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Drake Union, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Airport, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Property Management, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, OSU Hospitals Gift Shop, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Student Loan Foundation, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Physical Inventories, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, Transportation Research Center, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Audit Reports, General Receipts Bonds, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0006)
  - Internal Auditing, undated (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - University Press, December 13, 1979 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - University Press (petty cash), August 21, 1978 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - University Press (Accounts Receivable), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - University Press (Inventory), undated (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Bursar Special, June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Bursar (petty cash and balance sheet review), May 12, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Bursar (balance sheet), October 2, 1978 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Bursar (balance sheet), October 2, 1978 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Bursar (balance sheet), October 2, 1978 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Registration Services (change fund), January 17, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Testing and Evaluation (change fund), November 15, 1979 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (certification), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Schedule A), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Schedule C), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Schedule D), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Schedule E), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Permanent File), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Accounts Receivable), December 31, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Admin. File), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Accounts Payable), June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Telecommunication (Petty Cash), November 14, 1979 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Counseling and Consulting (Petty Cash), December 4, 1979 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - University Health Service: Pharmacy Inventory, May 31, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Student Financial Aid: Administrative File, June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
  - Student Financial Aid: Analysis File, June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1985.0187.0003)
- Accession Number UA.1986.0140, 1985 June 30; 0.02 Cubic feet; (1) letter file folder
  - Coopers and Lybrand Audit Reports for fiscal year, 1985 June 30 (Box Small Accessions 43)
- Accession Number UA.1988.0081, 1981-1984; 6.0 Cubic feet; (5) cartons
  - Music, School of, 1983 February (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Theatre, Dept. of, 1983 February (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Stone Laboratory, 1981 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Clear, 1981 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Black Studies, 1982 July (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - English, 1983 April (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Astronomy/Perkins Obser, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Chemistry (2 folders), 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Physics, 1982 November (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Psychology, 1983 March (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Administrative Science, College of, 1982 December (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Human Resource Research, Center for, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Management Science, 1982 December (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Marketing, 1983 January (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Meat Lab, 1983 February (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Farm Operations, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Educational Administration, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Education, College of, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Instructional Materials Lab, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Learning Resources, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Instructional Materials Production, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Civil Engineering, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Photography Cinema, 1983 January (Box UA.1988.0081.0001)
  - Pharmacy Administration, 1983 February (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Social Work, College of (2 folders), 1982 (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Center for Continuing Medical Ed, 1982 July (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Optometry (2 folders), 1982-1983 (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Veterinary Medicine Admin, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Veterinary Hosp (Assets Protection), 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Veterinary Hospital, 1981 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Graduate School Administration, Fall 1982 (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - University Press, 1982 July (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Mershon Center, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Library: Publications/Friends, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Health Sciences Library, 1983 January (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Student Aid Accounting, 1983 March (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Fees and Deposits (Investigative), 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Fees and Deposits(Assets Protection), 1982 December (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Fees and Deposits, Fall 1982 (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Treasurer's Office (Travel Audit), 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Accounts Payable, 1983 January (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Accounts Payable Leave Timekeeping, 1983 February (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Accounts Payable (Travel Audit 1/3), 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Accounts Payable (Travel Audit 2/3), 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Accounts Payable (Travel Audit 3/3), 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Academic Affairs, Fall 1982 (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Colleges of Arts Sciences, 1982 December (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Minority Affairs, 1983 June (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Health Sciences Library, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Lab Animal Center, 1981 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0002)
  - Univ Center for Int'l Studies, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Continuing Ed-Non Credit Programs, 1983 January (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Continuing Ed-Credit Programs, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - NCRVE, 1982 July (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - WOSU Year End Examination, 1981/1982 (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - WOSU, 1983 February (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Admissions Office, 1983 May (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Registration, Records, Scheduling, 1983 March (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Student Organizations Finance Office, 1983 April (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - SOFO Follow-up Review, 1982/1983 (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Student Life - USG Funds, Fall 1982 (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Counseling Consultation Service, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - University Health Service (2 folders), 1982-1983 (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Recreation Intramural Sports (2 folders), 1983 December (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Personnel Services, Fall 1982 (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Compensation Services (Special, 1982 November (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Child Care Center (2 folders), 1983-1984 (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Public Affairs, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Development Fund - Donor Confirms, 1983 June (Box UA.1988.0081.0003)
  - Business and Finance, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Contracts Administration, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - University Systems, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Business Management, 1982 December (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Purchasing, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Building Services, 1983 March (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Facilities Maintenance, 1983 February (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Utility Services - Fuel Oil Inv, 1983 June (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Grounds Maintenance, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Public Safety, 1982 November (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Business Admin, 1982 February (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - University Police (2 folders), 1981-1983 (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Traffic Parking, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Stores, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Print Facility, 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Dormitory Orientation Housing, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Dormitory Business Office, 1982 November (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - North Commons, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Athletics (Parking Review), 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Athletics (2 folders), 1982 November-December (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Athletics (Gladieux Review) 1/2, 1983 January (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Athletics 2/2, 1983 January (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Drake Bookstore, 1983 April (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Bookstores (Buy-Back Review), 1982 November (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Drake Union Bookstores, 1982 July (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Drake Bookstores, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Medical Bookstore, 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0004)
  - Ohio Union (4 folders), 1982-1983 (Box UA.1988.0081.0005)
  - Drake Union (New stand Inventory), 1982 August (Box UA.1988.0081.0005)
  - Drake Union (Food Service - Lease), 1983 March (Box UA.1988.0081.0005)
  - Property Management, 1982 September (Box UA.1988.0081.0005)
  - OARDC, 1982 July (Box UA.1988.0081.0005)
  - University Hospitals (Investigative), 1983 January (Box UA.1988.0081.0005)
  - Hospitals - Business Office (2 folders), 1982 October (Box UA.1988.0081.0005)
- Accession Number UA.1988.0083, 1982-1987; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  Audit Reports by external auditors (for state auditor) of OSU
  - Coopers & Lybrand, OSU Development Fund, Report to Management, Sept. 1985 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, OSU Development Fund, Examination of Financial Statements, Years ended June 30, 1984 & 1985 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report to Management, Year ended June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Compliance Examination, Two years ended June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Compliance Examination, Two years ended June 30, 1982 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Examination of Financial Statements, Year ended June 30, 1985 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Examinaiton of Financial Statements, Year ended June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Examination of Financial Statements, Year ended June 30, 1983 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Compliance and Management Report, June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Health Professions Student Loan Program, Nursing Student Loan Program, Scholarship Program for First-Year, Students of Exceptional Financial Need, Controls and Compliance Report, Financial Statements Reports, Year ended June 30, 1985 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Health Professions Student Loan Program, Nursing Student Loan Program, Scholarship Program for Firs-Year, Students of Exceptional Financial Need, Financial Statements Report, Year ended June 30, 1982 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Health Professions Student Loan Program, Nursing Student Loan Program, Scholarship Program for First-Year, Students of Exceptional Financial Need, Controls and Compliance Report, Financial Statements Report, Year ended June 30, 1985 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, National Direct Student Loan Program, College Work-Study Program, Supplemental Educational Opportunity, Grants Program, Pell Grants Program, Guaranteed Student Loan Program, Controls and Compliance Report, Financial Statements Reports, Year ended June 30, 1985 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, National Direct Student Loan Program, College Work-Study Program, Supplemental Educational Opportunity, Grants Program, Pell Grants Program, Guaranteed Student Loan Program, Controls and Compliance Report, Financial Statements Report, Year ended June 30, 1982 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Touche Ross & Company, The Ohio State University, The Ohio State University Hospitals, The Ohio State University Development Fund, The Ohio State University Housing Commission, Letters of Recommendations & Ohio Revised Code Compliance Letter, Year ended June 30, 1986 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
  - Touche Ross & Company, The Ohio State University, The Ohio State University Hospitals, The Ohio State University Development Fund, WOSU, Letter of Recommendations & Ohio Revised Code of Compliance Letter, Year ended June 30, 1987 (Box UA.1988.0083.0001)
- Accession Number UA.1988.0091, 1897-1947; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  - Audit reports by state examiner of OSU, 1897-1947 (Box UA.1988.0091.0001)
- Accession Number UA.1989.0121, 1980-1987; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  Audit reports, audit statements, compliance examinations, management statements, and correspondence.
  - Touche Ross & Company, WOSU - FM, CPB Annual Financial Report, June 30, 1987 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Touche Ross & Company, WOSU - TV, CPB Annual Financial Report, June 30, 1987 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Touche Ross & Company, WOSU Stations, CPB Annual Financial Report, June 30, 1987 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Touche Ross & Company, The Ohio State University, The Ohio State University Hospitals, The Ohio State University Development Fund and WOSU Stations, Letters of Recommendations and Ohio Revised Code Compliance Letter, June 30, 1987 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Touche Ross & Company, The Ohio State University, The Ohio State University Hospitals, The Ohio State University Development Fund and The Ohio State University Housing Commission, Letters of Recommendations and Ohio Revised Code Compliance Letter, June 30, 1986 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 5)